" THEY SEE YOU FROM WHERE YOU CANNOT SEE THEM "
You 're in a dream , Tarik . Wake up !
Wake up !
Soul becomes a stone .
Unless my mask is removed from the dirt , loneliness surrounding the earth
will be decorated with your apocalypse .
The dead gave life to your shadow . Tell me who you are .
He 's not answering the phone , Sema ?
He 's not answering .
He had a thing on the Internet . Maybe he 's still working on it .
It 's been days and I 'm not getting any news from him . It bothers me .
Well , I understand why he didn 't come here ,
but it 's silly not to answer the phone .
Girl , you 're so weird .
He asked you out and you said no . You told him to stay as friends .
Maybe not as much as yours , but men have pride , too .
Of course he doesn 't answer the phone .
But we call him from work . How can he know that it is Sema ?
Well , I don 't know about that , but Tarik recently bought a new computer .
After Sema rejected him , he locked himself in his home , turned into a computer nerd .
He had called me four days ago in the middle of a night . I was shocked .
I asked him what happened .
After he waited for a moment in silence , he said there was nothing and he hung up .
I don 't think Tarik 's behavior is about you , Sema .
Because a few days earlier , he did the same to me .
Well , maybe you 'll be surprised , but he called me a week ago , too ,
and said something I couldn 't understand in a whispered tone and hung up the phone .
Well , to be honest ,
Tarik got very strange after moving to that cottage .
It is so desolate at night .
I wouldn 't stay in that house even if they paid me .
You think he 's home now ?
Tarik , are you home ?
Tarik ?
- Can you do it ? - Almost done , ma 'am .
Just a second .
It 's open . There you go .
- Thank you . - Thanks , have a good day .
What happened to this place ?
What is it with all these tapes ?
Were you here all along ? You scared me to death .
Sorry , Hande . I didn 't hear you come .
You 're fine , right ? We 've been worried when we didn 't hear from you for days .
Why didn 't you answer the phone ?
I was working , dealing with stuff .
Did you finish your work on the Internet ?
No , I am not done .
You 've been working on it day and night for four days . What sort of work is this ?
- Can you tell me about it ? What is it ? - Never mind .
I just remembered , if you 're done with my camera , can I take it back ?
I 'm done , thanks .
It 's in the drawer right under the bookshelf .
Tarik , do you want me to open the windows for fresh air ?
For God 's sake , what is it with all these papers and tapes ?
Everywhere is a mess .
If there 's something I can do , I 'm free .
You know what ? Sema is really worried about you .
She thinks that you don 't call us just because of her .
Maybe you shouldn 't give up on her so soon .
Do you know what I mean ?
Tarik ?
Wake up now .
Wake up . Wake up now .
Wake up .
Wake up !
- Hello ? - Hello , Chief . It 's Haluk .
- Morning , Haluk . What happened ? - Maybe you should come a bit early today .
Station is under a lot of pressure now . A weird suicide happened yesterday .
HQ wants you to take care of this case .
- HQ ? - We received a call from Ankara .
Tarik Poyraz . 23 years old .
It looks like he killed himself with a big kitchen knife
at home at 4 : 40 p.m.
Initial reports suggest that there is no traces of violence .
The fingerprint on the knife belongs to him .
It seems like people knew him well . He was well liked .
He was making money on the Internet with some stock market transactions .
They said that he had been withdrawn lately .
The mess in his room shows us he had some psychological problems .
During the incident , he had a friend named Hande
who came to visit him at his home .
Both autopsy report and the girl tell us the same story . It 's suicide .
But the cause is unknown .
I 'm sorry , Chief .
Why is Ankara so interested in that case ?
We don 't understand that either .
They told us that as these kinds of deaths increase , especially in Istanbul - -
Never mind . You mentioned a girl . What is her name ?
Hande Çerkez . She is outside now .
Ms. Çerkez , Detective Süleyman Derviş is the head of this case .
He 'll ask you a few questions .
Your friend has committed suicide . So we do not suspect a murder .
From now , every detail you tell us will help us close the case . That 's all .
Miss Çerkez , can you please look at my face while I am talking ?
Why do you think your friend has committed suicide ?
I don 't know .
Have you ever thought about why people kill themselves by jumping into the sea ?
Because they see it as a soft , big pillow .
Or a compassionate hug from their mothers .
They believe they won 't feel any pain .
But the most terrible and painful way of death ...
is by drowning .
I mean , the way of suicide
may give us more clues than the real reason .
Just like your friend 's case .
It doesn 't look like a typical suicide , right ?
Miss Çerkez , please look at my face while I am talking .
What happened in the house that day ?
Did you finish your work on the Internet ?
No , I am not done .
You 've been working on it day and night for four days . What sort of work is this ?
Can you tell me about it ? What is it ?
Never mind !
I just remembered , if you 're done with my digital camera , can I take it back ?
I 'm done , thanks .
It 's in the drawer right under the bookshelf .
Wake up !
Wake up now !
You 're in a dream , Tarik !
Wake up !
Hande , what happened ?
I saw Tarik in my dream .
Why did he kill himself in such a terrible way ?
Guys , I don 't think one of us is guilty .
Suicide does not happen just like that .
It 's a way of expressing secrets and pain .
We thought that we knew him .
Last week , he told me that he wanted to travel to the Far East for a vacation .
He was so normal . You know , sometimes you 're just lost in your thoughts ,
he wouldn 't even do that .
Actually , this Internet thing made him into someone darker .
I warned him all the time , " Stop working , go outside . "
I wonder what the cops are thinking . What did you tell them ?
Miss Çerkez , please look at my face while I am talking .
What happened in the house that day ?
We were chatting . It was normal .
He just looked ... really tired .
The whole place was covered in black tapes and newspapers .
When he came near me , he opened the cabinet and took something .
Then he went to his room .
I asked him about my camera which I gave him .
He said he 's finished with it .
After I took my camera , I heard him screaming horribly ...
" Wake up ! "
- Then - - - I know what happened afterwards .
Okay . I will ask you one last question . This one is important .
As far as I understand ,
Tarik was really interested in computers and the Internet .
Do you think he might have anything to do with new religions or cults ?
I 've known him for many years ,
and I 've never heard of anything like that .
He wasn 't interested in those kinds of things .
He just earned money on the Internet .
So you did not tell the cops that he got rejected by Sema four days ago ?
Don 't be ridiculous , Cem .
You were the one saying
that it cannot be related to Tarik 's suicide .
All right , don 't get mad !
I 'm just worried .
And only a fool would go to the police to report this .
Never mind . Tarik didn 't have much luck with women anyways .
He was almost incompetent .
Buddy ... I still can 't believe it .
It isn 't me .
No !
You are not real !
You don 't exist !
Go away ! You can 't come in !
You can 't come in ! Go away !
Get out .
Where are you ?
This is what separates humankind from others .
We forget death easily .
And that is the right thing .
Now that I think of it , many people from my childhood are dead now .
I cried after each .
Especially after my wife .
But after a short time , your grief disappears .
- That 's life ! We need to be strong ! - Hello , how are you , uncle ?
Thank you . Welcome . We were chatting with Sema .
- How are you ? - Good . My mother called me .
" You can come back to Istanbul , " she said . I told her that I 'd stay for a while .
It 's good idea . We need each other at these times , anyways .
When we 're done with this stuff , we can go sailing with my uncle 's boat .
We can go to the island that I told you about before .
Girls .
Ready to see something really weird ?
- What ? - What sort of ...
I was checking my emails .
I think you 'll find one of them interesting .
- What ? What is that ? - Wait a minute .
Look at the mail at the top . The one with " 388 @ 0 . "
- Yes ! This is Tarik 's address . - And the delivery date is today .
LET ME OUT !
How does a man who died three days ago send an e-mail ten minutes ago ?
What does it say ? Open it !
This is the most interesting part .
A weird picture attached next to the writing " Let me out . "
It is Tarik .
Did you look carefully at that part ?
What is that ?
Look carefully .
- Do you see it ? - His pupils don 't exist .
- How could this be possible ? - What are those in the background ? Humans ?
Really , what are those ? What are they doing ?
- Make it bigger . Hurry up ! - All right , don 't panic .
Who took this photo ?
It could be Tarik .
But the worst part is that it 's coming from a dead man .
Is it possible that someone is using his emails ?
Who ?
I don 't know .
- The tape in my camera ... - What ?
Never mind , I don 't think they are related .
Let 's just drop it .
' Cause I don 't feel good .
CRIME SCENE - DO NOT CROSS
Hello ?
What happened , Haluk ? Did you get the results ?
They were not able to get anything from the boy 's computer , Chief .
They did not ? Why is that ?
Those computer technicians on the force were only able to get these ?
What is this ?
Oddly enough , they told us this is the first time they saw such a thing .
They didn 't find any viruses on his computer . This is all they got .
" 388 @ 0 . "
Do you see what I 'm dealing with ?
Any guess what this is talking about ?
I 'm going out . I 'll buy bread , some eggs , and chocolates for myself .
- Do you need something ? - No , thanks .
Okay , see you .
The suicide spree is taking over America right after Japan .
News of deaths all across the country , consisting mainly of young people ,
is taking its toll on the American population .
Although the exact number is unknown ,
it is estimated that 1,337 people committed suicide in the last week .
Although some fail to pay attention , the US authorities are in panic .
Our friend , who is currently in America , is on the line to report the latest news .
Yasemin , could you tell us what is going on in the USA ?
At first , nobody was paying attention to the suicides happening in New York .
Even the US media covered only a few of these incidents in the news .
As deaths are rising quickly like a virus all around the country ,
and the death toll reaches thousands , the government has issued a red alert .
While some people continue to live as they were , some are in panic .
Some suggest that this has become the worst incident since 9 / 11 .
Especially , the college students ...
So , the United States superpower is under severe stress now .
Politicians and clergymen are trying to calm down the public .
But the fear that spreads across the country now
is not caused by either war or terrorism .
Hande , is there something wrong ?
I was lost in my thoughts , and when I heard the bell ...
God !
How is this possible ?
Who is he ? What is he doing ?
What is this ?
Are you ready to flip your reality upside down ?
No !
388 @ 0 IS CALLING
Hello ?
- Hello ? - My veins are bursting apart !
If somebody told me I would face such things , I 'd just laugh .
The most interesting part is that I really don 't know what 's going on .
" Are you ready to flip your reality upside down ? "
I don 't know what it means , but this is not normal for sure .
Tarik 's suicide was not normal , either .
What do you mean ?
I did not want you to watch it ...
but Tarik shot weird things with my camera .
I took my camera back from him that day .
There was a tape .
I don 't believe you .
How could you hide something like that from us ?
I did not hide it , Sema . I was too scared .
- I did not want you to be scared , either . - What did you see in those videos ?
He was screaming as if someone was in his house .
And he was covering each and every gap with black tape and newspapers .
He was crying and slapping himself in a weird way at the same time .
Wake up now ! You 're not real !
Wake up now ! Wake up !
Wake up !
Show yourself ! Where are you ?
When I looked out through the window , I saw you two .
But you were not there when I opened the door .
It was weird . It was like we were dead .
Enough . I 'll go back to Istanbul tomorrow .
Because I don 't feel good .
Sema , I will give the tape and the picture of Tarik to the cops .
I cannot let you go to Istanbul like that .
Cem , send that picture of Tarik to me via e-mail .
I will give it to the cops with the tape .
Keeping you away from the cops will be better .
All right .
Detective , there is something on the news that might concern us .
Thirty-four people committed suicide in Istanbul .
So investigations have started
on whether they are related to the ones in the USA .
But authorities are avoiding commenting on that .
Our guest is psychiatrist Ahmet Taşlı . Welcome , Mr. Taşlı .
Hello .
Sir , would it be logical to think that these cases are related to the ones
that happened in the USA and some places in Europe ?
First of all , I want to emphasize that we do not have a specific age group .
Up to this point ,
no medical or forensic conclusions have been reached .
There is only one common thing , which is the Internet .
So can we say that it is related to a new religion or trend
that operates on the Internet ?
There is an idea from the USA which says
that there is a cult that hypnotizes and drives their members to suicide ...
and works efficiently and secretly on the Internet .
With that , they get rid of the issues of religion , language , race , and border .
But I want to present a different point of view .
Today , when it comes to science , the USA is the best , right ?
However , even they are going through a nightmare .
And all scientists are definitely desperate about that .
I 'll keep it short . I think the world is entering a new era .
I believe that humanity is facing something
that is beyond science and it is very serious .
Could you elaborate ?
I am a scientist , after all .
My comment on this issue which concerns humanity is clear as day .
Some metaphysical elements that we don 't know ,
and thought of as impossible until now , are becoming active .
Some incidents that we ignore because they 're metaphysical
have become irrefutable now .
None of the incidents , suicides , murders can be explained scientifically .
This is like a shift in dreams and reality . It is hard to accept .
But if we ignore that , a danger awaits the world .
Especially when people say , " We 're in a Muslim country ,
nothing will happen to us . "
This is the highest level of ignorance and irresponsibility .
In short , authorities should form a committee immediately and ...
I have a question for you .
Is it possible to say
that someone who takes his own life has also committed a murder ?
If the victim and the murderer are the same person ,
how can we say that it is murder ?
Even if it were , then shouldn 't someone who attempted suicide
also be charged with murder ?
So we cannot say it is a murder , right ?
Yes .
As the homicide bureau , why do we have to deal with this case ?
I want two things from you .
First , investigate whether this " 388 @ 0 " thing
is a common thing among the cases in both Istanbul and the USA .
And the second one is to try and find the meaning of " 388 " in any religion .
Yes , Chief .
Come in .
Chief , someone is calling for you .
Who ?
Dead guy 's friend . The one who committed suicide .
Her name is Hande .
I 'll take this tape .
We 'll speak to you after analyzing it in detail .
Can I mail you the picture that I mentioned ?
Of course .
Here is my e-mail address . You can send it here .
By the way , the subject line of Tarik 's email said " 388 @ 0 . "
We didn 't understand what it was , but it might be helpful for you .
We have seen it in the data of Tarik 's computer .
We don 't know what is means . My colleagues are trying to find out .
I don 't think it 's something important .
However , I have to go .
It 'd be better not to use the Internet very much these days . Just in case .
- Good evening . - Thanks . You , too .
- We 'll see each other again . - Okay .
Okay , Mom .
I 'm fine . I will stay here for a bit longer .
Yeah . Okay .
You said it yourself , here it is safer than Istanbul .
Hande is cooking right now .
Say hi .
She says hi , too .
Okay , Mom . See you .
Did Tarik use to have weird habits ?
No , he didn 't .
From whom or what do you think he was running from in that video ?
I don 't know , but it sounded real .
Cem ...
I wonder what he is doing .
Hello ?
Get me out of here .
Who is calling ?
Save me .
Get me out of here .
Who are you ?
" I am in a dream right now . " " I am in a dream right now . "
What the hell is that ?
What did you do , Tarik ?
What ?
Let me out !
Mommy !
- Hello ? - Hello .
Help me !
My veins are bursting apart !
Doesn 't he answer ?
It 's ringing , but he doesn 't answer .
I wonder what happened .
I wish I had told him to stay with us tonight .
Never mind . We will call him tomorrow .
Why do you think suicides have suddenly started to happen all over the world ?
What I could not understand is how the biggest fear of all , death ,
could become alluring to some ?
If all of them are suicides , of course .
None of them knew each other . So what else is possible ?
I don 't know .
Honey , you 're hungry , aren 't you ?
I will cook something up .
I won 't cook any fried food .
You should be careful about your cholesterol .
From now on , you will eat boiled vegetables , salad , and fruits .
I won 't even tell you to quit smoking .
Just like the doctor said , the formula is easy .
The forbidden three .
Flour , sugar , and salt .
But there is one more thing .
You tell me what it is .
Water !
Yes , honey .
Water .
Why did you cheat on me ?
Love is a poison .
What ? What do you mean ?
How could you do that to me ?
You cheated on me .
Don 't be ridiculous , Sultan .
You must be kidding , right ?
Thanks to you , I have discovered the most painful side of being cheated on .
Do you want to know what it is ?
- Sultan ! - You cheated on me ,
even though you love me ! This is what is suffocating me !
This is what is suffocating me !
Hello ?
Good morning , this is Haluk .
Sorry for waking you up this early .
Hello ?
Yes , Haluk . What is the problem again ?
Chief , one more of them died last night .
CRIME SCENE - DO NOT CROSS
Twenty-three years old . Cem Terzioğlu .
Drop that gum .
Sorry , Chief .
He knows the girls . They saw each other yesterday .
Even though how he died is unclear , it doesn 't look like a murder .
Forensic medicine wanted us not to touch the body until they arrive .
The girls told us they don 't know anything .
We 're now at the scene of the second mysterious death incident in a week .
As it resembles the other incidents all over the country , especially Istanbul ,
it seems that the public is very nervous .
And when the Word is fulfilled ,
against them we shall bring forth from the earth
a Beast to speak unto them because mankind had no faith in our signs .
The Ant , Verse 82 .
Here is the Koran . Here is the verse .
Did someone take away your sight , your hearing , and seal up your hearts ?
Dabbe is responsible for all the killings . Dabbetu 'l-arz !
It is among us . It spreads like a spiderweb .
Dabbe is using djinns .
Dabbe is using djinns . Dabbe is ...
Shut up !
Goodbye , kid . Have a good journey .
Thank you , Uncle Ali .
Say hello to your mother and father .
- Call me right after you land . - Sure .
Are you mad at me because I 'm going ?
No , why would I be mad at you ?
Besides , we can 't put your mother in distress .
Please take care of yourself , okay ?
You , too . No more being sad .
No more being sad .
Chief , the police commissioner is coming .
Okay . All right .
The situation is terrible , Süleyman . We got a fax from Ankara .
They 're waiting for a detailed explanation about the deaths in two days .
They called me at least ten times today .
If you cannot give me something tomorrow , we are in trouble .
Chief , solving these cases is not easy .
To understand the relation between the cases in Turkey and the world - -
Forget about the world .
You will put us in deeper trouble if you carry on doing this .
People are agitated , trying to find a scapegoat .
Your duty is simple .
Write your report , put it on my desk .
We 'll send it to Ankara and get rid of it .
Yes , sir .
Let 's just hope
that the press doesn 't show the video clip of that madman .
Otherwise , we 're in trouble .
Dabbe refers to a thing that spans like a web
in the ancient Indian language .
Dabbe is one of the keenest verses in the Koran .
Dabbe will appear
close to Judgment Day .
It will fall upon the world .
All djinns will obey Dabbe .
According to us , djinns are the ones that are in the mirror .
When the masks will fall down ,
when hearts will turn to stone ,
when shadows wake up ,
when reality is flipped upside down ,
when all djinns will rush into the world
and bow down to Dajjal ,
when Mahdī sheds tears and challenges Dajjal ,
just be sure
that the Judgment Day is upon you .
- Hello ? - Hande , it 's me , your uncle . How are you ?
I have been calling your landline , but it was busy . Are you okay ?
I 'm fine , uncle . Thank you .
I was on the Internet , that 's why it was busy .
I came home after I sent Sema off .
Do you need anything ? If you want , you can come over .
Thank you , uncle .
I have work to do .
If I feel bad , I can call a cab .
Okay , kid . Take care then . Will you come to work tomorrow ?
Yes , I will , uncle .
I 'll see you in the morning . Good night !
Okay . You , too .
" Djinns ... according to us ,
they are the ones that are in the mirror . "
Dabbe is responsible for all the killings . Dabbetu 'l-arz !
Here is the Koran . Here is the verse .
It is among us . It spreads like a spider web .
Dabbe is using djinns . Dabbe is using djinns .
" Dabbe . "
Cem .
Cem . What happened to you ?
Dabbe !
" Dabbe . "
Chief , here is the summary of the last findings .
One , the reason for the deaths is not clear ,
but it looks like a sudden act of insanity .
Two , we didn 't find any connection with illegal groups .
Three , which is important , the sign " 388 @ 0 " is common all around the world .
Yet , what it means remains unknown .
Did you find anything about the tunnel that we saw in the first guy 's picture ?
I sent for all railway tunnels from State Railways . We 'll get it by tomorrow .
By the way , I even got scared from the picture while I was looking at it .
That man ...
Where is that man ?
We need to talk to him .
Calm down , Hande . Catch your breath first .
Which man ?
The one shouting with the Koran today .
Police took him away .
I want to see him right now , please .
We already released him .
He was known as a mad and isolated man
living in a village near Şirince .
He 's not mad .
I don 't know where and how he knows .
Actually , he told us what " 388 @ 0 " means .
If you could be more clear , we would understand , too .
What is written here ?
What about now ?
" Dabbe . "
Ziya !
Look at us ! We want to ask you something .
This man won 't listen .
Dabbe .
How did you find out it was Dabbe ?
I shouldn 't have told you !
I shouldn 't have told you ! I shouldn 't have !
I shouldn 't have !
They 'll hurt both me and my wife !
Do you have a wife ?
- Of course I do . - Where is she then ?
She is here , looking at us .
You don 't have a wife . If so , why don 't we see her ?
You can 't see her because my wife isn 't a human .
She is a djinn .
Is she watching us right now ?
Yes !
What is her name ?
Tıgıl .
Her name is Tıgıl .
Tıgıl ?
Was she the one who told you about Dabbe ?
Yes . She told me that Dabbe is killing people by using djinns .
But they were angry at us .
Because of what we say , they will kill us .
From now on , djinns will become visible to humans .
They will be everywhere .
We 're almost there !
- There is somebody else here . - Who is it ?
She says that she 's your wife . But your wife is dead , isn 't she ?
Ziya , cut the crap !
Djinns can imitate both dead and alive .
So , why can 't we see them ?
They see you ...
from where you cannot see them .
But from now on , we will see them as well .
They found a way to make themselves visible .
Because - -
If djinns have the technology , is it possible they control the Internet ?
It 's ridiculous .
Is it ridiculous to find " Dabbe " in all the suicide mails ?
I prefer to link this to a group of people called Dabbe rather than djinns .
What about what people saw ?
Sometimes all of us are prone to hallucinations or weird dreams .
Even I deal with them .
What happened to your wife ?
Hello ?
Hande ? Good luck , kid .
- Thank you , Uncle . - Have you called Sema ?
I 'm calling her right away .
Uncle ?
Are you there ?
Who are you ?
What do you want ?
You are not real !
No !
Doomsday !
Hello ? Haluk , where are you ?
Chief , I have good news . I have found the tunnel .
I had it cleaned . You are the only one who knows for now .
Where are you ?
Chief , there is a path behind the Seven Sleepers Cave . I am at that path .
On my way .
Is anyone there ?
NEW MESSAGE
There is a path behind the Seven Sleepers Cave .
Come to the end of that path .
Damn ! Perfect timing . Work , damn it !
Who is that ?
Hande !
Mr. Derviş !
I 'm inside the cave . Come here !
Come here !
Come inside !
Hande !
Mr. Derviş !
Are you there ?
Mr. Derviş ? What are you doing there ?
WORSHIPING THE SHADOWS ?
Dajjal !
Subtitle translation by Oguzhan Uygun